恐らく 具現化系能力者の技だな。
I came up with that strategy...
[TEL]　ああ　間違いない。
ten years ago.
昨日は　なかった建物で 密集している。
I was pretty happy
どう考えても　「念」だ。
that a fool like me could figure
out a smart strategy...
ビルまで具現化しちまう奴が いるなんてよ。
But then, I saw how to defeat it.
何らかの仕掛けがあると思って いいだろう。 [TEL]　ああ　奴らが　まだ
That the Supreme Leader thought
of the same strategy as I had...
ここをアジトにしているって 証拠でもある。 問題は　建物が密集しているせいで 死角が多過ぎるんだ。
I was so honored and touched...
My heart trembled. It felt like...
どうしても　廃虚全体の ２割程度しか把握できないぜ。 [TEL]　かといって やみくもに動き回って 鉢合わせになるほうが もっとマズいな。
Like seeing my child brought back to life.
俺も　それは　ごめんだし。
Foolishness.
今だって　もし突然 背後から奴らの声がしたら
I've had enough. Get some rest.
どうしようって 心臓バクバクいってんだからさ。 声か…。 [TEL]　ん？
Once we begin again, you won't get any more breaks.
いや　分かった。
Be prepared!
ウボォーから聞いた 鎖野郎の情報というのは
But I don't understand why...
ノストラードファミリーの 構成員を調べてた時
That I do not understand my own mind
ウボォーが 「こいつらだ」って言ってたのが
upsets me more than words can describe!
そこで　その娘から 能力を盗んだんだな。 ああ。
Did she not choose to rest?
そして　こっちが最新の ボディーガードの写真リスト。
No...
もう　新しい情報に 変わってたのか。
Unsightly.
ボディーガードが７人 もしくは　それ以上か。
No sign of intelligence or dignity.
娘っ子１人に　大層なこったな。
How can such a being
親バカなんだろ。
boast a Gungi record so stellar
that it could be called
娘自身より その能力のほうが大事なようだ。
the ultimate in game theory?
それを面白く思っていない連中も いるんだろう。
Wake up! We're starting again.
でも　何で　このコ ヨークシンに来たのかな？
Y-Yes...
はい。 ナイスだ　というか　俺はバカだな。
9-5-1, marshal.
クソ…　どうかしてた。
For this match...
なぜ　ボスの娘は ヨークシンに来たか。
Hmm?
そこに俺が気づいていれば
We should make a wager.
もっと早く 鎖野郎に　たどり着いていた。
A wager? Correct.
この娘がボディーガード付きで ヨークシンに来た目的…。 それは やはりオークションだろう。
If you win, I shall grant
any wish you request.
占いの能力にばかり気をとられ 重要視していなかったが
Any wish I request?
サイトの情報によると この娘には
Any wish...
人体収集家という もう一つの顔がある。
However...
人体…　緋の眼か！ ああ　鎖野郎がノストラードファミリーに 入ったのは　たまたまじゃ　ない。
If you lose, I shall take your left arm.
俺達への復讐と　仲間の目の奪還。
Fear and desire hold the power
シャル　奪った競売品の中に 緋の眼はあったか？
to disrupt one's rhythm.
ごめん…　分からない。 競売の最中は 進行役を自動操作にしてたから。
Desire clouds vision, while fear stills one's step.
コルトピ　緋の眼を コピーした覚えはあるか？
My left arm...
確か　コピーした。 お前のコピーには 「円」の効果がある。
コピーが 今　どこにあるか分かるか？ 本物を触ればね。
Should I do it?! Why do you hesitate?
あったよ。
Well... Instead of my left arm...
分かった　同じ形のものは あっちの方角。
My life.
大体２５００ｍ。 そこに鎖野郎が…
If I lose, I will offer you my life.
急いだほうがいいよ。 「円」の効果は あと数時間で消えちゃうから。
But you might consider that an insult...
地図あるか？
I do not understand.
はい。
Explain yourself.
ホテル・ベーチタクル。
Well, Gungi is really the only thing I can do.
いいだろう　ただし　俺と一緒だ。
But professional Gungi players, even national champions, make but a pittance.
了解！ パク　マチ　シズク お前達も一緒に来い。
Only after you become the world
champion as representative for a nation
シャルは　コルトピと交代だ。 ＯＫ！
will you receive any meaningful reward.
[TEL] もしもし。 [TEL]　あっ　キルア君？ ああ　あんたは？
To become the national representative,
you must win tournaments.
[TEL]　クラピカの仕事仲間 左のほうを見てくれる？
In other words, you cannot lose a single match.
ん？ [TEL]　ケータイ切って すっごい小声で 私に何か命令してみて。
I come from a family of twelve, and in our home, I'm the breadwinner.
右手　上げて。
If I lose a single match, I will become the greatest burden on my family.
すっげぇ地獄耳 こいつは使えるな
Gungi players have a saying... That, after losing once, a Gungi master
becomes a normal person.
あん？ そこは行った所じゃねえのか？
If I lose, I'll be garbage.
ホテル・ベーチタクルは ノストラードファミリーの
Ah, it doesn't bother me!
宿泊先の一つだったろ？
It's just what my parents always said...
ああ　でも　シャルが この前　サイトを調べた時には チェックアウト済みだったはず。 同じホテルに 別名義で借りていたんだろう。 なかなか肝が据わっている。
So, the day I set my sights on
becoming a professional player, I decided that if I ever lost a match,
I would take my own life.
雨音で内容は聞き取りづらいけど 確かに　あの敷地内で話してる。
But that could be a problem...
足音からみて５６人 女も交ざってる。
How so?
廃虚から出て 反対側に向かってるわね。
When I lose, I'll become garbage...
すげぇな 俺もゴンも鍛えてるほうだけど
And all you'd receive for
winning would be garbage.
全然　聞こえねえ。 そういう能力だから。
That would be a terrible insult.
クラピカも　だいぶ 切羽詰まってるみたいね。
It doesn't bother me.
私にまで協力を求めるなんて。
I'm more interested in learning
what you'd want if you win.
あの人 全部　自分でやりたがるでしょ。
You see...
あ…　ああ　確かにね。 あなた　まさか殺し屋さん？
I've spent all of my time thinking about Gungi...
元だけど　何で分かるの？
I'll think about it later, after I win.
足音よ。
Very well.
こんなに近くにいても エスティントだから。 エス？
Then she possesses neither desire nor fear?
今まで会った人の中で 一番静かよ　すごい技術だわ。
Your life, was it? It appears I was the one lacking in resolve!
クラピカが　あなたを頼る気持も 分かるわね。 まっ　こっちは嫌々なんだけどね。
I never imagined that, if you won,
you might ask for my life.
あら　そうなの？ ストップ！
Your Majesty! Silence!
この道を曲がって １００ｍくらい
The Supreme Leader's l-li—
その先に奴らがいるわ。
I w-would never ask such a thing!
他の足音と区別つくの？
The thought never crossed my mind!
癖があるのよ それぞれ微妙にね。
I know that. The fault is my own.
へぇ　ちょっと見て来る。
The wager is off.
[TEL]
It was a petty tactic.
キルア？ [TEL]　あの女がいたぜ。
No...
それと　あと１人　俺達が 昨日　見ていない奴がいる。
Accept this apology.
こいつ　恐らくリーダーだ。
Your Majesty!
[TEL]　どんな奴？
How could you do that?
黒いコート着てる 背中に逆十字付きの。
I must treat your arm... Come with me!
黒髪でオールバック 顔は見えない。
Y-Your arm? Continue the match.
ってか　隙なさ過ぎ！
Huh? Huh?
[TEL]　正面なんか 怖くて回れねえよ！
What happened, Supreme Leader?
代わってくれ　今　どの辺りだ？
It's your turn. Make your move.
[TEL]　モトバビル前。 [TEL]　コンチネンタル通りを 西のほうへ歩いてる。
Your Majesty... We must stop the bleeding!
[TEL]　状況によるね 混雑してれば何とか。
Do not make me repeat myself.
レオリオ　南へ向かってくれ。
Continue the match.
ＯＫ！
It was I who said there would be no more breaks.
センリツが同じ車両で 張っててくれてる。
I shall summon Neferpitou.
カスツール方面行きの電車だ。 俺は　最後尾に乗ってる。 カスツール方面。 競売市があるのも　こっちだね。
I am sure that you can continue to play, as your arm is reattached.
私達のホテルも 同じ方面にあるな。
That is the best compromise I can offer.
ああ　ああ 分かってるよ　エリザ。 俺だって　こんな仕事 もう　うんざりだ。 「かわいい犬と一緒に いられるからいい」だって？
If you refuse to accept it, you may take my head now!
フッ　そりゃあ　わがまま娘の
Very well.
お守りよりは楽だけどさ。
Come closer.
ネオン様は好きだけど 元気過ぎて　私…。
I shall end it with a single strike.
[TEL]
It's your turn.
まぁ　もう少し辛抱してくれ 今に　もっと　いい仕事を…。
Make your move. I refuse. I refuse to move before you
have your injury treated.
ルームサービスです
Don't make me repeat myself.
Make your move.
よし　食おう。
At once!
なかなか　ねえよなぁ。
There's no doubt. All the puppets have vanished.
ん？
Have they resumed the selection process?
大丈夫だって 俺に任せときな！
No, I doubt it. We have the capital surrounded.
[TEL]
My assumption would be that
some threat greater than us
[TEL] 降りたか
has befallen the Royal Guard,
or upon the King himself.
リバ駅って所で降りた。 サロマデパート方面口に 向かってる。
So this is it?
マズいな　ホテルの方向だ。
Our golden opportunity?
[TEL]
Yes...
マジかよ！ 部屋を替えたのが　バレたのか！
Our chance to infiltrate the palace.
クソ！　冗談じゃねえ！ 急いで　ズラかるぜ！
However, it may be a trap.
これだけは 持って行かねえとな 駅は　そこだ もっと近くに行ったほうが
That shouldn't be the case... They wouldn't use any tactic that
might endanger the King.
いいんじゃねえか？ ダメだ
They would if the King ordered it.
これ以上　近づくと　私の敵意に 相手が気づく恐れがある。 ゴン　ここから駅の入り口まで
I suppose... Regardless, they've retracted
their long-range radar.
この距離が　私の間合いだ。
We should use this chance to
get as close as possible.
奴らに存在を気づかれずに 攻撃できる距離。 ここから攻撃が到達するまで 約０．５秒。 奴らほどの使い手ならば 余裕で　かわせる時間だろう。
I must create a portal near the palace, or the plan will fail.
何かに　気をとられない限り。
This dangerous job had to be done eventually.
「クモ」！
I found them.
動いてる。
It appears Cheetu failed.
エレベーターだな　出掛ける気か。
Try not to die.
急ごうぜ　団長。 これから　全員で捕獲にかかる。
Same to you.
互いにフォローできる 間合いを保て。
They've split up for us.
パクノダ　敵を捕まえたら ウボォーのことを聞き出せ。
I found them.
了解。
We'll switch to the man with the pipe!
その後は　ノブナガ… 好きにしろ。
Let's go!
夕方のラッシュの時間だ 車より　奴らのほうが 早いかもしれねえ。
Doctor Blythe.
６人は 北西方向に走ってるってよ。 ああ　私が追ってる。 [TEL]　まさか走って追っかけてんのか ヤバいって！
7-9-1, spy.
絶対　気づかれるぞ　すぐ中止…。
2-3-1, pawn.
[TEL] おい！ チッ　切りやがった　あの野郎。
How long will the operation take?
ん？ ん？
I'd say two or three hours
until complete recovery. And during that time, you cannot use
either your puppets or En, correct?
すっごい　何？　あれ 忍者だ　忍者！
This ability requires a lot of Nen.
２時の方向へ 時速４０ｋｍほどで移動中。
A great deal of energy is needed to recreate flesh.
車に乗ったな。
While you treat His Majesty,
I shall watch the surroundings.
次の仕事が見つかるまで とか思ってたが　とてもじゃねえ。
Though my En is nowhere as effective as yours.
今日で最後だ！ [TEL]　レオリオ　ゴンは？
Regardless, this is an important task
that I cannot trust to anyone else.
ラッシュで　全然　進まねえ！ だ！　もう分かった！ 俺達もクラピカを追う！
As expected, I cannot sense any En use...
ったく　どいつも　こいつも 勝手に動きやがって！
The rain helps to lower visibility.
つけられてるな。
Soon, the sun will set.
いつから？ ヤバっ　追うのに夢中で 気づかなかった。
Once it is night, I can hide in the darkness.
前と後ろ　どっちが鎖野郎だ？
And picking out enemy aura will be easier.
ノブナガ　パクノダ コルトピ　前を追え。
Be patient.
了解！
The closer the portal is to
the palace, the better.
見えたか？ 影だけ　姿までは。
While I can enter and exit freely, Shoot and the rest can only use
the portal to leave once they enter.
でも　路地に１人。 ゴミ箱の後ろに１人。 ＯＫ　「凝」を怠るな。 了解。
If the enemy prepares an ambush by the exit, it will mean serious trouble.
「クモ」め…　来るなら来い！ ダメだ　クラピカ！ こんなに警戒された状況で ３人を相手になんて
I must prepare three exits in the area
around the palace, one near, one far, and one somewhere in between, then
place entrances even further away.
勝ち目がない！ よし　イチかバチか
I'll set up the entrances in groups of three,
in locations where the palace is within sight.
ゴン!? ごめんなさい！
When the mission starts, we can enter
by the most convenient location.
もう　追っかけないから 許してください！ また　この子？
Once it's time to act, the situation will determine
whether we approach
こいつか？　例の子供は。 もう１人いるだろ　出て来な！
by the near exit, the far exit,
or the one in between. Once that has been determined, we act.
何の用だ？ もう私らに　賞金　懸けてる マフィアは　いないよ。
From the enemy's perspective,
we will be appearing from nowhere.
えぇ！　ホント？　どうして？
We must use that opening to separate
the King and Royal Guard.
どうする？　団長。
That is when our battles will begin!
捕まえろ。 [TEL] フィンクスか？　俺だ。 ベーチタクル・ホテルまで 来てくれ。
It doesn't matter if we finish with a 1-3 record, so long as the King is their one loss.
１つ聞きたいことが あるんだけど。 なぜ　自分達と かかわりのない人間を殺せるの？
Under normal circumstances, I would already be within
range of Neferpitou's En. This is quite tense...
白旗を揚げた割に 敵意満々といった顔だな。
must be on the palace grounds,
or it won't be any use to us! Advance carefully, but swiftly!
なぜだろうな 関係ないからじゃないか？
Should I wait for the sun to set?
いや　あらためて問われると 答え難いものだな。
But, will this scenario hold out until then?
動機の言語化か あまり好きじゃないしな。 しかし　案外… いや　やはりというべきか…。
I have no choice... Should Neferpitou's En return, approaching the palace will be impossible.
自分をつかむカギは そこにあるか…。 何だ　こいつ…
If I fail, we still have other options!
このままホテルまで行き フィンクス達を待つ。
I have nothing to fear.
逃げようとしたら殺していい。 了解。
Advance... Advance...
相手が集中している以上 最低でも　この距離を保たないと 奴らの警戒網に引っかかるわ。 もちろん ちゃんと気配も消してね。
In the palace, there are three humans not intended as food.
クソっ！ 焦りは禁物よ。 分かってる！
The first is the Gungi player.
分かってないわよ！
The second is Diego.
あなたの無謀な追跡で ２人が危険にさらされているのよ。
And the third...
分かってるの？ あなたが　ここで見つかったら
is Secretary Bizeff.
誰も「旅団」を 止められないからよ！ クッ！
Behind the scenes, he was
the country's true ruler.
すまない。
All dealings with foreign parties
and domestic organizations
どんな人間だって 隙は必ずできるわ。
went through him as an intermediary.
根比べよ　焦らないで。 ああ。 スクワラは？ ケータイに出ないんだ。
Since he cannot be replaced, he is the only human allowed near the King.
鎖野郎じゃないね。
No human guards are posted near the palace.
降りろ。 俺は　これでも そこそこ腕は立つ 修羅場を　いくつも抜けて来た
Because ordinary soldiers would
be powerless against Nen users, the Royal Guard determined that the
presence of ordinary soldiers would, in fact, increase the risk of infiltration.
そういう者だけに働く 勘がある
The only Squadron Leader present
is Cheetu, who has just returned.
その勘が　いっている
There are only six other Captain and Soldier Ants.
俺は　ここで… 少しでも動いたら切るぜ。 グッ。 いくつか質問するから 正直に答えて。
In other words, there are currently only three humans
and eleven Ants in the palace.
あんたの仲間に 鎖を使う奴がいるでしょ。
The Soldier Ants are
今　どこ？
the various Squadron Leaders' personal troops.
何の話だ？ お前ら　一体　何者だ！
Thus, they are not involved
in the King's protection.
俺を　ノストラードファミリーの者だと…。
Essentially, the Squadron Leaders
次　左手　折るわよ。
no longer have any strict fealty to the King.
おい！ 動くなって言ったろうが。
They work together simply
because their goals align.
直立不動で聞かれたことだけ 答えろ　ボケ！
Understanding this, Pitou and the Royal Guard
あんた達が　さらった 大男のことよ。 あぁ　逃げたよ　そいつは 後のことは知らねえな！
have assigned those Chimera Ants tasks
that are expected to end in failure.
他の仲間は　どこ？
Hence, they would not be trusted
with monitoring the palace.
ひと足先に　シマに戻ったよ 俺も帰るとこだったんだ。
However, Knov does not know this.
うっ…。 ウソは　いけないわね。 本当だって！　こんな状態で デタラメ言うわけねえだろ！ もう一度　聞くわよ 鎖の使い手は　どこ？
As he attempts to infiltrate the palace, he has no idea that this is
his best, and last, chance.
最後の質問。
I managed to survive somehow...
あなた　大切な人　いる？
But on my own, I can only work so much.
そんな奴がいたら こんな仕事してねえよ！
I must convince them
ふん。 エリザっていうの。
to at least provide three more
staffers to do secretarial duties...
そのコ　美人ね。
Otherwise, I'll die of overwork.
捕らわれたゴンとキルアを救うべく 走るクラピカ 決戦の時は もう間近まで迫っていた
This is it. He took the bait, Palm-kun!